http://www.ever-so-sexy.com/privacypolicy.html

Update 03/08/2020Severe delays for goods shipping to Canada.We have received notification that post into Canada is experiencing extended delays due to COVID 19. Because of the increased risk of lost parcels in these circumstances, we will not be shipping to Canada until the situation improves.Update 24/04/2020We are continuing to ship. We may not always be able to ship on the same day as your order during this difficult period and unfortunately, there are delays in the distribution network which are beyond our control. So please order at the earliest opportunity.  Keep well and keep safe.Privacy PolicyEssili.com is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information you give us. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UKThe purpose of this statement is to tell you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.When you place an order with us we need to know: your name billing address and delivery address if different email addressThese details are needed to process and ship your order.Offline Payments: If you request an offline card payment, we will request your credit card information and process the order, taking the payment immediately. Your card details are then destroyed with no paper or electronic record kept.Online Payments: If you choose to pay online either via Secure Trading or PayPal we do not store, have access to or see your credit card information.In order to process credit/debit card transactions, the bank or card processing agency may require to verify your personal details for authorisation outside the EEA (European Economic Area). Your information will not be transferred outside the EEA for any other purpose.We only use your personal information to notify you of your purchase, the order progress and to send you updates on our products and services.Our newsletter: We will only send our newsletter with your consent.We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial purposes beyond the essential requirement for credit/debit card validation during the purchase.We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with the UK data protection legislation.We do not collect sensitive information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it to us. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update and remove your personal details by logging into your account or by contacting us.Cookies: We use a technology called cookies as part of a normal business process to track patterns of behaviours of visitors on our site and to enhance user experience. A cookie is an element of data that our website sends to your browser which is then stored on your system. It will not damage your system and is non-intrusive. You can set your browser to prevent this happening but certain site behaviours will not work, for instance, the shopping cart will not "remember" contents so you would need to order each item one at a time. We also use Google Analytics which makes use of the cookie technology. Again this is used to monitor user behaviour. The data is anonymous and aggregated and does not affect your privacy.If you have any questions about our privacy policy please contact us.Delivery by Royal MailBe among the first to know about new designs. Receive exclusive offers and useful information and enhanced discounts.E-mail Address: *Name:Country:Sign me upSign me up  Join us on facebookFollow us on twitterRead our blogCopyright © 2006 - 2020 Essili is a trading division of Crysalis Ltd. Registered in England No 05922306              Sign In : New Account View BASKET : £0.000LingerieEroticSexy Lingerie SetsSexy NightwearBodies & BodysuitsBodystockingsOpen Sexy Bras & Quarter Cup BrasCheeky-Panties - Sexy KnickersSexy ThongsChokersCuffsGlovesMasksOpen Cup Basques and BustiersTops & SkirtsSilkBras & Bra SetsTeddiesCamisoles & Cami SetsChemisesSilk Knickers & Lace PantiesJackets & RobesBodysuitsBasques & CorsetsSilk Suspender BeltsBrasBalconetteBridalLong LinePaddedGlamorous Push UpHalf PaddedSoft CupStraplessBralette or TrianglePanties & SuspendersSuspender BeltsKnickers & PantiesThongs & G StringsBridalGartersStockings & TightsNightwearCamisoles & Cami SetsLong NightdressesNegligees, Jackets, Tops and Dressing GownsPractical NightwearShort NightdressesWomen's Pyjamas & NightshirtsBrandsAxamiBeauty NightBracliCoemiDikiGorteksGracyaIrallJane WoolrichLiliana CasanovaLola LunaLuxxaProvocativeRoza LingerieShirley of HollywoodSonata RapalyteInfoLoyalty PointsContact usNewsletterSizing GuideAbout UsShippingReturnsCookiesPrivacyTerms & ConditionsSite MapNewLate GiftSwimwearBikinis & TankinisOne Piece SwimsuitsHealth & Safety
